movs.ch 2013-12-21

# - Movs.ch

  * **Information you provide:**  
When you sign up for a movs.eu Account, we ask you for personal information. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other movs.eu services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information.
  * **Cookies:**  
When you visit movs.eu, we send one or more cookies to your computer or other device. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad selection, and tracking user trends, such as how people search. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some movs.eu features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.
  * **Login formation:**  
When you access movs.eu services via a browser, application or other client our servers automatically record certain information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, your interaction with a service, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account.
  * **Third Party Applications:**  
movs.eu may make available third party applications, such as gadgets or extensions, through its services. The information collected by movs.eu when you enable a third party application is processed under this Privacy Policy. Information collected by the third party application provider is governed by their privacy policies.
  * **Other sites:**  
This Privacy Policy applies to movs.eu services only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results, sites that include movs.eu applications, products or services, or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.
  * **User Data:**  
movs.eu never shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of movs.eu under any circumstances.
  * **General:**  
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.
